你好  库柏探员
25年后再见
与此同时
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     苏小黛 胖爱 Silence 小仓 吃冰棒 詹木头 小酸奶
翻译     Lynn_宁  TheWalkingNerd  一只虾  Reginamoon
校对     小酸奶
时间轴     啾啾啾  吃土少女  知之
后期     8T
双峰  第三季第一集
总监     小酸奶
库柏探员
听
那声音
它现在
在我们的家里了
是的
It is.
现在  这些都不能
大声说出来了
记住
理查德和
琳达
一石
二鸟
我明白
I understand.
你
离得太远
博士
Hey, Doc.
乔
Hey, Joe.
怎么样  博士
How's it going, Doc?
一如既往的好
As good as ever.
好了
All right.
需要帮忙吗  博士
You gonna need any help, Doc?
这个嘛
You know,
谢了  但不用了
thanks, but no, thanks.
我喜欢单干
I like to work alone.
纽约
三号机
Camera three.
有外卖
Delivery.
-特雷茜  -你好
- Hey, Tracey. - Hey.
你不用亲自送过来的
You didn't have to bring it yourself.
你不是应该在工作吗
Aren't you supposed to be working?
没有  我十点就下班了
No, I-I got off at ten.
我带了两杯
I brought two.
能跟你一起吗
Can I join you?
该死
Damn.
特雷茜  很抱歉  这里闲人免进
Tracey, I'm sorry, but no one can come in here.
我该给你多少钱
How much do I owe ya?
不用了
No, no, I--
我没花钱
I got 'em for free.
我不能进去吗
I can't come in?
是的
That's right.
该死
Shoot.
最高机密
Top secret.
那我更好奇了  你快把我逼疯了
Now I'm so curious. You're driving me crazy.
我得进去了
In fact, I got to go back in.
我明天来上班的时候去你那  如果可以的话
I'll stop by on my way in tomorrow, if I can.
好的  要是我想你了
Okay, or if I miss you,
我也可以明晚再来
I can come back tomorrow night
带上咖啡  同一时间
and bring coffees, the same time.
谢了  特雷茜
Thanks, Tracey.
两杯都给你吧
You can have 'em both.
谢了  特雷茜
Thanks, Tracey.
你真是个坏姑娘  特雷茜
You're a bad girl, Tracey.
你试试看啊
Try me.
贝弗莉
Beverly,
告诉豪斯曼女士
tell Mrs. Houseman that we will
我们会退她两晚的住宿金
refund two nights of her stay
但一整周可不行
but not the whole week.
她和她纽约的朋友们
She and her New York friends
一直使用着我们的按摩馆呢
keep our SPA running.
好的
Good.
臭鼬到底怎么进到她房间里的
How did the skunk get in her room?
什么
What's that?
臭鼬
The--the,  skunk,
怎么进到她房间里的
how did it get into her room?
不  没有
No, no, no, no.
根本就没
It--it wasn't even--
都没靠近她房间
even close to her room.
臭鼬在酒店的另一头
The skunk was on the whole other side of the hotel.
-是...  -我来了
- It was... - I am here,
本老弟
Brother Ben!
酸酸甜甜
Sweet and sour,
带点咸  很松脆
salty, crunchy...
贝弗莉
Beverly,
这是我弟弟杰瑞
my brother Jerry.
你好  很高兴见到你
Hi. Nice to meet you.
去找豪斯曼女士吧  就按我们说的
So get back to Mrs. Houseman as we discussed...
-好的  -我回头找你
- Okay. - and I'll get back to you later.
当然
Sure thing.
那个是新来的女孩吗
Is that the new girl?
还是我应该称呼为"女人"
Or should I say "Woman"?
那样的一个女人你不能称之为女孩
A woman like that, you can't call a girl.
贝弗莉  是的
Beverly, yes.
你上她了吗
Are you banging her yet?
杰瑞
Jerry!
尊  重
R-e-s-p-e-c-t.
尊重
Respect.
她是一个美丽的灵魂
She's a beautiful soul.
而且她结婚了
And she's married.
以前你可不介意这个
That never stopped you before.
给我吧  给我吧  给我吧  给我吧
Sock it to me. Sock it to me. Sock it to me. Sock it to me.
杰瑞
Jerry.
你脑子里还能有什么
What else do you have on your mind?
实际上我在神游
Swimming in my mind at this time, literally,
思绪从我最新研究的水栽籼粳混合稻
is my new hydroponic indica-sativa hybrid,
一路通过阿姆斯特丹快速通道
a touch of the mythic AK-47
跑到神秘的AK47
by way of the Amsterdam express.
它被烘焙成了香蕉面包
It's baked into this banana bread
又被灌入了这个可以抹平的果酱之中
and infused in this potent spreadable jam
这对于孤独的创造者来说再理想不过了
that's ideal for creative sojourns of a solitary nature.
思绪泛滥
Wheels up.
杰瑞
Jerry,
吃自家旅馆东西的创始人
a prophet is without honor
是不会获得别人的尊敬的
who eats his own profits.
那可不对  本老弟
Not indeed, brother Ben.
这让我状态正佳
It puts me in a groove,
没有人知道我什么时候会累
and where it stops, nobody knows.
感谢上帝你再也不插手宾馆的工作了
Thank God you are no longer in the hotel business.
你怎么了  本
Where have you been, Ben?
我的最新合规合法的业务
Yeah, my new legally sanctioned business
是把我们的税收翻三倍
is tripling our revenue.
这是妈妈的帽子吗
Is that Mother's hat?
双峰警察局
露西·布伦南
你好  我想找杜鲁门警长
Hello. I'd like to see Sheriff Truman.
哪一个
Which one?
杜鲁门警长不在吗
Sheriff Truman isn't here?
你知道哪一个吗
Well, do you know which one?
可能会弄错
It could make a difference.
不  女士
No, ma'am.
一个生病了
One is sick,
另一个去钓鱼了
and the other one is fishing.
可能会弄错
It could make a difference.
是关于保险的
It's about insurance.
我不确定我能否帮上你
I'm not sure I will be able to help you.
我要见杜鲁门警长
I'd like to see Sheriff Truman.
我会留下我的名片
I'll leave my card
改天再打电话来
and call in another day.
谢谢
Thank you.
我会留好名片的
I'll keep the card,
但是除非
but unless--
你以为你在往哪里走
Where the hell do you think you're going?
瞧瞧
Well, lookee here.
奥蒂斯
Otis.
你好  比尤拉
Hello, Buella.
你好吗
How you?
比尤拉
Buella,
雷和达雅
Ray and Darya--
你把他们带回来了吗
have you got them back there somewhere?
我去叫他们
I'll get 'em.
还有  比尤拉
And, Buella,
装饰一下你的前门吧
put something better at your front door.
世界上都是卡车司机
It's a world of truck drivers.
雷
Ray!
达雅
Darya!
雷
Ray,
达雅
Darya,
我们走
let's go.
C先生  C先生
Mr. C. Mr. C.
再见  奥蒂斯
See ya, Otis.
特雷茜
Hey, Tracey.
他不在这里
He's not here.
没人在这里
No one is here.
真的吗
Really?
好奇怪
Weird.
他去哪儿了
Where is he?
这说明我可以
Does this, by any chance,
跟你一起进去吗
mean that I can go in there with you?
我又带了两杯拿铁来
I brought us two lattes again.
那么
Well,
既然没人来阻止你
since there's no one here to stop you,
我想你可以进来一会
I guess you could come in for a little while.
但我不知道如果保安回来
But I don't know how you're gonna get out
你要怎么出去
if the guard comes back.
我们先别去想这种可能性
Let's not overthink this opportunity.
那是什么
What is that thing?
一个玻璃箱
A glass box.
但是用来做什么呢
Yeah, but what's it for?
我真的不知道
I really don't know.
只是我帮学校做的一个活
It's just a job I got to help with school.
这地方是谁的
Whose place is this?
听说是个亿万富翁的
I heard a billionaire.
某个匿名富翁
Some anonymous billionaire.
好神秘啊
Mysterious.
我得留心观察这个箱子
I'm supposed to watch the box
以防里面出现些什么
and see if anything appears inside.
什么
What?
会有东西出现吗
Do things appear?
从开始到现在  我什么都没看到
I haven't seen anything since I started.
但是我取代的这个人
But the guy I replaced,
他看到过一次
he saw something once.
什么
What?
他不肯告诉我
He wouldn't tell me.
或是不能告诉我
Or couldn't tell me.
我们不该说起这个地方
We're not supposed to say anything about this place
或是那个玻璃箱
or that glass box.
好多设备
It's a lot of equipment.
是不是某种科学实验
Is it some sort of science experiment
或是类似的东西
or something like that?
我想你也可以这么说吧
I guess you could say that.
你要不要坐下
Do you want to sit down?
好
Okay.
很舒服
Cozy.
给  你的咖啡
Here's your coffee.
谢谢你  特雷茜
Thanks, Tracey.
你要不要亲热一会
Do you want to make out a little?
你觉得呢
What do you think?
停下
Stop.
怎么了
What?
南达科他州鹿角镇
怎么了  阿姆斯特朗
What is it, Armstrong?
露丝
Ruth.
露丝  你在里面吗
Ruth, are you in there?
我的老天爷
My goodness.
我们走  走吧  阿姆斯特朗
Come on. Come on, Armstrong.
走  阿姆斯特朗
Come on, Armstrong.
走
Come on.
来  阿姆斯特朗  来
Come on, Armstrong. Come on.
来  小乖乖
Come on, little you.
好
Yeah.
天呐
By golly.
喂
Yes, hello?
你们不认识我
Yeah, you don't know me.
我叫玛乔丽·格林
This is-- this is Marjorie Green.
但是我的邻居不对劲
But my neighbor, there's something wrong.
我三天没见到她了
Yeah,  I haven't seen her in three days.
然后有一股难闻的气味
Oh, and then there's that terrible smell.
阿姆斯特朗闻到了
And Armstrong smelled it in the--
然后我闻到了  不是
Then I smelled it-- No.
不是  阿姆斯特朗是我的狗
No, Armstrong's my dog.
不是  我的地址吗
No-- Oh, my address?
我不知道
I-I-I don't know.
老天爷
My goodness.
是  我知道的
Yes,  I know this.
我知道的
You know, I know this.
太好笑了
It was a funny thing.
我打电话给你们的时候
I couldn't remember my address
我不记得我的地址了
when I called you on the phone.
臭味从哪发出来的  格林太太
Where's the smell coming from, Mrs. Green?
又来了
Oh, there it is again.
就是这股臭味
There's that smell.
女士  这里的管理员有钥匙吗
Ma'am, is there a manager on-site with a key?
我不知道
Oh, I don't know.
巴尼平时都在这里
Barney's usually here.
你要我去找找他吗
Do you want me to go check?
要的  女士  如果你不介意的话
Yes, ma'am, if you don't mind.
我刚想起来了
Oh. I just remembered.
巴尼不在这里
Barney's not here.
巴尼很幽默
He's a funny one, that Barney.
他现在医院
He's in the hospital,
不是普通的医院
not the regular hospital.
达琳
Hey, uh, Darlene,
派个开锁匠来箭头路1349号
we're gonna need a locksmith over at 1349 Arrowhead,
或许是1054号
possible 10-54.
不  不对  是1349号
No, no, 1349.
女士  谁住这间房
Ma'am, who lives in this apartment?
露丝  露丝·达文波特
That would be Ruth, Ruth Davenport.
我又想起一件事
And I just remembered something.
什么事  女士
What's that, ma'am?
巴尼每次离开镇子
When Barney's out of town,
都会把钥匙留给他兄弟
he leaves the keys with his brother.
他兄弟是谁
And who would that be?
我不知道
Oh, I don't know.
我从来没见过
I've never met him.
但汉克认识他
But Hank would know him.
汉克是谁
Who's Hank?
巴尼的朋友  汉克·菲尔莫尔
Barney's friend, Hank Fillmore.
我们去哪儿能找到汉克
Where would we find Hank?
那个...
Oh, well...
这会儿我也不知道
I don't know right now.
他是我们这里的修理工
He's our maintenance man.
但我刚才看到他回来了
But I saw him out back a little while ago.
哈维
Harvey?
哈维  你个混蛋
Harvey, you son of a bitch!
你是汉克吗
Are you Hank?
你们搞什么鬼
What the hell?
我们是警察  菲尔莫尔先生
Police, Mr. Fillmore.
我们需要你的协助
We need your help.
是哈维叫你们来的吗
Did Harvey send you?
菲尔莫尔先生  我们急需
Mr. Fillmore, we need a key
露丝·达文波特的房间钥匙
for Ruth Davenport's apartment.
我们正在找巴尼的兄弟
We're trying to find Barney's brother.
谁告诉你们我正要去见奇普的
Well, who told you I was going to see Chip?
谁是奇普
Who's Chip?
巴尼的兄弟
That's Barney's brother.
我们要找奇普拿钥匙
We need a key from Chip.
我刚才正要去找他  但是
I was just on my way, but h--
你们是怎么知道的
how did you know?
你知道齐普的电话吗
Well, do you have a phone number for Chip?
不  不  不
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
齐普
Chip?
齐普不用电话
Chip ain't got no phone.
我们还是等锁匠吧
I'll wait for the locksmith.
抱歉
Excuse me.
也许露丝出镇了
Do you think that maybe Ruth's out of town?
为什么
Why?
实在是不好意思
Well, it would be a shame
因为她出远门的时候
'cause I'm supposed to water her plants
我会去帮她浇花
when she's out of town.
我有她房间钥匙
I have the key.
走吧
Let's go.
我  我可以走了吗
Am I-- am I free to go?
先生们  我可以走了吗
Gentlemen, am--am I free to go?
哈维  你这个混蛋
Harvey, you son of a bitch.
是你把条子叫过来的吗
Did you send the cops to my place of business?
我的事儿
My work?
哈维  是的
Harvey-- Yes.
当然  我拿到了
Yeah, I got it--
我全拿到了
I got all of it,
就在手上  但这都是我的
right here, but it's mine.
是我和齐普的
Mine and Chip's.
不  你已经退出了  记得吗
No. You opted out of this one, remember?
哈维  哈维  别
Harvey-- Harvey, don't--
别恐吓我  哈维
don't threaten me, Harvey.
哈维
Harvey.
Harvey?
康斯坦丝
Constance?
为你高兴  戴夫
Good for you, Dave.
你现在改头换面了
You're behaving yourself for a change.
过来帮下忙好吗
Want to help me with this?
小心点
Very carefully.
把它拿开  别碰到尸体
Keep it way up, off the body.
霍克副局长
Deputy Hawk,
玛格丽特·兰特曼一号线呼叫
Margaret Lanterman's on line one.
副局长
请切换进闪光的那条线路
It's the line with the light that's blinking.
好的  露西  谢谢你
Okay, Lucy, thank you.
玛格丽特  有什么事吗
Margaret, what can I do for you?
霍克
Hawk.
我的木头要告诉你一条消息
My log has a message for you.
我听着呢
Okay.
我丢了点东西
Something is missing,
你得找到它
and you have to find it.
线索就在
It has to do with
和戴尔· 库柏特工有关
Special Agent Dale Cooper.
戴尔· 库柏
Dale Cooper?
是什么
What is it?
你会发现
The way you will find it...
和你的遗产有关
...has something to do with your heritage.
这是我的木头要给你的信息
This is the message from the log.
好的  玛格丽特
Okay, Margaret.
谢谢
Thank you.
晚安  霍克
Good night, Hawk.
晚安  玛格丽特
Good night, Margaret.
鹿角镇警局
正在上传扫描件
上传完成
找到匹配
戴夫
Dave?
Dave!
就来
On my way.
你来看看这个
You got to see this.
头肯定是露丝·达文波特的
The head is definitely Ruth Davenport,
就是住在公寓中的那个女人
the woman who lived in the apartment.
还有一个无名男性
And we've got a male John Doe.
我们不知道这是谁的身体
We don't know whose body that is.
查不出这些指纹是谁的
Nothing's come back on those prints.
但是还有另一组指纹
But there's another set of prints
遍布整间公寓
all over the apartment.
我们已经查出来是谁的了
And we've got a hit,
确定是属于本地人的
a definite local hit.
比尔·黑斯廷斯
Bill Hastings?
天呐
Oh, my God.
是的
Yeah.
他是我孩子的校长
He's my kid's principal.
戴夫
Dave!
-你来干什...  -菲莉斯  比尔在家吗
- What are you-- - Phyllis, is Bill home?
-在  -谁来了  亲爱的
- Yeah. - Who is it, honey?
是戴夫  戴夫·麦克利
It's Dave, Dave Macklay.
戴夫  你好
Dave, hey.
怎么了  伙计
What's going on, buddy?
比尔
Bill, uh,
我得逮捕你
I'm gonna have to put you under arrest.
-什么  -请转过去
- What? - Please turn around.
我得把你拷上  带你回局里
I've got to cuff you, and I've got to take you in.
天呐  比尔
Oh, my God, Bill!
-不  这...  -天呐
- No, it... - Oh, my God.
没事的  亲爱的  我什么坏事都没做
It's okay, honey. I hav-- I haven't done anything wrong.
能告诉我是因为什么事吗
Could, uh--could you tell me what this is about?
我们可以在局里说
We can talk about that at the station.
我想跟你一起去
I want to come with you.
不不  待在家  他们肯定是搞错了
No, no, stay here. There's been a mistake.
好吗  我什么坏事都没干
All right? I haven't done anything wrong.
你有权保持沉默
You have the right to remain silent.
你所说的任何话都将
Anything you say can and will be used
成为呈堂证供
against you in a court of law.
但摩根一家马上要来吃晚饭了
But the Morgans are coming for dinner!
你了解我刚说的权利吗
Do you understand these rights I am--
我非常了解
I understand perfectly.
打给乔治说下我的情况
Just call George and tell him where I am!
她说过有什么东西丢了
She said something is missing
而且和库柏探员有关
and it has to do with Agent Cooper.
但库柏探员失踪了
But Agent Cooper is missing.
在沃利出世前
And he hasn't been seen or heard from
都还没有他的消息
since before Wally was born,
现在沃利都24岁了
and Wally's 24 years old.
他和马龙·白兰度是一天生的
He was born on the same day as Marlon Brando.
安迪想给他取名为马龙
Andy wanted to name him Marlon.
我们还没有收到过库柏探员的圣诞节贺卡呢
And we haven't even gotten a Christmas card from Agent Cooper.
他都没有见过沃利
He hasn't even seen Wally.
安迪  露西  不早了
Andy, Lucy, it's late.
去仓库把那些我刚才说的文件拿来
Go down to storage and get those files that we talked about.
明早  把它们全都摆在桌面上
Tomorrow morning, lay 'em all out.
我会带咖啡和甜甜圈来的
I'll bring the coffee and the doughnuts.
好的  霍克副局长
Okay, Deputy Chief Hawk.
戴夫
Dave?
唐·哈里森   拉皮特城州警局的
Don Harrison, State Police, Rapid City.
你来接手这个案子吗
Hmm, are you taking this case?
还是你的案子  戴夫
It's yours, Dave.
我只是来帮忙的
Just here to help.
失踪的身体和头有消息了吗
Any luck with the missing body and head?
没有
Nothing.
他关在这里多久了
How long's he been in there?
差不多一个半小时了
About half an hour.
也差不多了
That's enough.
你真的不想接这个案子吗
You sure you don't want to take this?
迈克说你们两个是渔友
Mike said you're fishing buddies.
我从高中起就认识他了
I've known him since high school.
他对你估计会更坦诚一点
He might tell you more than he'd tell me.
进去吧
Go on in.
抱歉拖了这么久
Oh, I'm sorry about the delay.
他们有没有给你端杯咖啡什么的
Uh, did they get you some coffee?
我喝水就行
I'm good with the water.
你能不能...
Can you--can you, uh,
能不能告诉我出什么事了
can you please tell me what's going on?
我会说的  不过有几个问题
We'll get to that, but I have a few questions
你得先回答我一下
that I have to ask you first.
你认不认识露丝·达文波特
Do you know a Ruth Davenport?
名字挺耳熟的
That name sounds familiar.
是那个图书管理员吗
the librarian?
-是的  -好的
- Yes. - Ah, okay.
就是她
That's her.
你认识她吗
Do you know her?
不大认识
Not really.
最多打个招呼
We say hello to each other.
你最后一次见她是什么时候
When did you see her last?
我也不知道
Oh, I don't know.
让我想想
Uh, let me think.
大概几个月前
Maybe a couple months ago?
你有没有去过露丝·达文波特的家里
Have you ever been to Ruth Davenport's home?
没有  从没去过
No. I've never been there.
我都...  我都不知道她家在哪
I don't--I don't--I don't even know where she lives.
你有没有去过位于箭头路1349号的
Have you ever been to the apartment building
那栋公寓楼
at 1349 Arrowhead Road?
没有
No.
没去过
I never have.
我从来...  从来都没去过那里
I-I--I've--I've never-- I've never been there.
你...  你能不能告诉我这是怎么回事
Could--could you please tell me what this is about?
你拿到逮捕令了吗
Did you get the warrant?
马上就好
Any minute.
法官在爬山
Judge was up the mountain.
比尔
Bill,
你能说说你在最近几天
can you account for your time
都干了些什么吗
over the last three or four days?
好的  当然可以
Sure, yes, I can.
我工作日每天都在学校
Uh, I've been at school every weekday.
晚上呢
And evenings?
这是我们的高中校长
Our high-school principal.
周三我放学之后直接回家了
Uh, Wednesday, I went home right after school.
周四的时候我们
Thursday, we had
在晚上开了个会
a-a meeting in the evening.
之后...
And then...
我就回家了
...I went home.
然后...
And then...
周五我去...
uh, Friday, I went--
我出去吃了个晚饭  和菲莉斯一起
I went out to dinner, Phyllis and I.
吃完我们就直接回家了
But we went home right after that.
我今天一整天都在家
And--and I was home all day today.
那个...
What--what--
周四的会是干什么的
what was this Thursday meeting about?
关于授课的
Curriculum.
教学评估
F-faculty evaluation.
两个月开一次
It's a bimonthly meeting.
什么时候结束的
And when did it end?
大概是九点半吧
Around 9:30, I believe.
我也记不清了  我们还点了披萨
I don't know. We ordered pizza.
那...
And...
你之后就直接回家了
you went home directly after?
是的
Yes.
你几点到的家
And what time did you get there?
十点十五  二十左右吧
At 10:15, 10:20.
你一般回家要多久
Well, how long does it take you to drive home usually?
周四会议
9点30结束  10点15到10点20到家
对了
Oh, yeah--
对了  我想起来了
oh, yeah, now I remember.
我把...
I gave...
我的秘书  贝蒂  送回家了
...my assistant, Betty, a ride home.
她当时有点...
Something wrong with her...
她的车出了点毛病...
car, something wrong...
我想和乔治说句话
I think I'd like to speak to George.
他是我的律师
He's my lawyer.
他...  他来了没有
Is--is--is--is he--is he-- is he here?
我去看看
I can check.
不过比尔  在把律师叫来之前
But, Bill, is there anything else
你还有没有别的事
that you would like to tell me
想要跟我说
before we get the lawyer involved?
请你告诉我到底出了什么事
Please tell me what's going on.
露丝·达文波特被谋杀了
Ruth Davenport was murdered.
她的公寓里到处都是你的指纹
And your prints are all over her apartment.
什么
What?
带黑斯廷斯先生去他的新房间
Show Mr. Hastings to his new room.
他可以在那见他的律师
He can meet with his lawyer there.
好了  你现在得跟我走了  比尔
Right, you're gonna have to come with me now, Bill.
走了
Right out here.
左边  比尔
To the left here, Bill.
就是这里  比尔
Right--right here, Bill.
戴夫
Dave,
我能联系一下菲莉斯吗
could I speak to Phyllis?
你能让我  让我和她谈谈吗
Could you let me-- could you let me do that?
我看看能做些什么
I'll see what I can do.
黑斯廷斯夫人
Mrs. Hastings,
我们有你房子的搜查令
we have a warrant to search your house.
真是难以置信
This is unbelievable.
我们今晚还要招待客人
We have guests for dinner tonight.
车道上的是比尔的车吗  女士
Is that Bill's car in the driveway, ma'am?
是沃尔沃
It's the Volvo.
我们需要用一下钥匙
We'll need the keys.
戴夫
Dave?
必须这么做  菲莉斯
It has to be done, Phyllis.
我们进去了
We're coming in.
走
Let's go.
我的手电筒坏了
My flashlight's broke.